I'm making a little video.
Want to earn my money?
The little video will save your business.
Brother.
This one is the stop.
I'll walk anyway.
It's already starting.
You still have to get the chevas,
play a piece.
Oh,
a lot.
No,
not closed.
Hello and I entered.
My God,
it's closed.
Nobody saw how it is then,
okay?
Three left.
The store was closed.
But I can't waste time because I'm on foot,
right?
crazy,
good morning,
I need to increase my contact network.
You're on,
crazy,
oh bro.
Gives license
the barbershop here every time I come here,
zero truffle guys' stock,
bro.
I do the good one here,
find a place that gives movement that will sell you much more mano.
I'm using the client's bathroom here,
man,
it gives the most tummy ache.
It took the weekend there,
João.
Thanks, huh? Bro,
beautiful thing,
call me there,
bro said,
I'm going there on an auto part,
I'll take you there.
I need to find 1 fuel bomb per Chevette.
It's 1 point 4,
1 point 6 respects bro there's no history worse than I don't have a young
man oh don't say that bro I don't really have a bro for a change don't you?
What's up,
brother?
Pretty, Man,
I need 1 fuel pump for the Chevette 86 Chevette.
I will not have a brother.
There are none that can be adapted.
No, Cara,
Chevette's bro is just him.
140 tale bro,
I go down even not soft closed,
it was worth it.
Good weekend to you,
here we go.
There are times when we try to self-ate old,
but it's difficult,
then you manage to do a nice little thing and then
comes the problem and then I'm testing several things,
a thousand things go to my head.
Lots of pressure,
bro.
Today is being one of the hardest days for me to do this series.
I wanted to record this,
this is on.